[{"answer": "I'm a little battered and bleeding, but --", "docId": "130206pmt", "aSentId": 32, "question": "And Dick Morris, how are you?", "qSentId": 31}, {"answer": "I absolutely believed it, and so did a lot of people.", "docId": "130206pmt", "aSentId": 50, "question": "Is there any rational explanation for why you got it so wrong?", "qSentId": 49}, {"answer": "Well, (INAUDIBLE) when he was a mayor of New York, said, I don't make many mistakes, but when I make them, it's a beaut.", "docId": "130206pmt", "aSentId": 58, "question": "How can a pundit who is as experienced as you, with great respect, be so wrong when this guy just sits on his computer, crunching the numbers and data, and gets it completely right?", "qSentId": 57}, {"answer": "Well, I have gotten 30 senators and governors elected, 14 presidents and prime ministers.", "docId": "130206pmt", "aSentId": 108, "question": "How does that make you feel, given you've been so respected for so long until this period?", "qSentId": 107}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130206pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "You mean Hurricane Sandy?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "I think all the polls should be taken with a large pinch of salt.", "docId": "130206pmt", "aSentId": 134, "question": "Well, I prefer to believe that CNN's polling was accurate, wouldn't you?", "qSentId": 133}, {"answer": "No, but --", "docId": "130206pmt", "aSentId": 161, "question": "Was that why FOX let you go?", "qSentId": 160}, {"answer": "Well, I had a wonderful talk with Roger Ales, who I really respect, a week ago.", "docId": "130206pmt", "aSentId": 189, "question": "But they must have told you, isn't it?", "qSentId": 188}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "130206pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "Why have you been singled out?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "No, I don't.", "docId": "130206pmt", "aSentId": 205, "question": "But do you know the answer?", "qSentId": 204}, {"answer": "Look, FOX has given me the opportunity of a lifetime.", "docId": "130206pmt", "aSentId": 210, "question": "Do you resent the decision?", "qSentId": 209}, {"answer": "Piers, when --", "docId": "130206pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "It's got to annoy you that Karl Rove gets to stay there, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "No, I'm saying that they're not going to do that, and that's their opinion.", "docId": "130206pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "Should the party's stand then for a woman's right to choose was to trying to keep the numbers low, is that what you're saying?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "But what I am --", "docId": "130206pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "Where does the party stand?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "Pro life.", "docId": "130206pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "What's the Republican position then?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130206pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "What you're saying is, they need to move from pro life to pro choice, albeit trying to reduce the numbers?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "No, you're not.", "docId": "130206pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "Am I right?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "My view on gay marriage is that if a state decides to go for gay marriage, the legislature of the voters, that's great.", "docId": "130206pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "-- that so many states are moving that way?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "I don't believe that the court should jam it down anybody's throat.", "docId": "130206pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "What's your personal view?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "That if people want it, they should be able to do it, but it's got to be a decision of the community.", "docId": "130206pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "What's your view?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "What we do stand for, Republicans do stand for, and it's becoming very clear, and we need to be much stronger on this, is holding down spending and debt.", "docId": "130206pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "It can't have endless people on both sides ripping each other's position apart, so that people (INAUDIBLE) when it comes to an election, people go, what do they actually stand for?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "Well, I don't -- a fight of that sort now would be destructive.", "docId": "130206pmt", "aSentId": 326, "question": "Should Boehner - should he be replaced?", "qSentId": 325}, {"answer": "Well, I thought he was graceful, first of all.", "docId": "130206pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "Where do you start with all that?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "Well, I -- you know, I think we have to really start with the laws.", "docId": "130206pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "Never mind specific weapons, but the culture of gun violence that has enveloped America?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "I was up on Capitol Hill today, and speaking to 15 members of Congress, and all of whom have said that they are for this legislation.", "docId": "130206pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "But is there a will amongst the politicians, Kerry Kennedy, to get this done?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "Well, the most important thing is to keep lethal weapons out of the hands of criminals and the mentally ill and people who would perpetrate that violence.", "docId": "130206pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "What is your solution or idea for how to reduce gun violence in America?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "Well, the AR-15 is a civilian version of the military rifle, and is widely owned legally by the civilian community right now.", "docId": "130206pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "What is the big deal in extending the limitation, in the light of these mass shootings, to include assault weapons, assault rifles?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "They're not the military version.", "docId": "130206pmt", "aSentId": 574, "question": "What is the argument against banning them?", "qSentId": 573}, {"answer": "I'm not sure.", "docId": "130206pmt", "aSentId": 597, "question": "How does it feel to be an icon?", "qSentId": 596}, {"answer": "Incredible moment, Kanye West in my office rapping his entire album to me, just like we're sitting here, right.", "docId": "130206pmt", "aSentId": 602, "question": "Of all your amazing successes with all these incredible artists, what's the one, if could I relive it for you again -- you have like five minutes to live and I could say you can have one moment with any of these artists, which one would you go for?", "qSentId": 601}, {"answer": "Yes, absolutely.", "docId": "130206pmt", "aSentId": 605, "question": "ORGAN: Did you know the moment you heard it, this would be huge?", "qSentId": 604}, {"answer": "I think it is great for his brand.", "docId": "130206pmt", "aSentId": 611, "question": "Is the Kim Kardashian move good for his brand or devastating?", "qSentId": 610}, {"answer": "Let's talk about Beyonce quickly, the lip syncing debate.", "docId": "130206pmt", "aSentId": 615, "question": "What's wrong with that?", "qSentId": 614}, {"answer": "I would think.", "docId": "130206pmt", "aSentId": 634, "question": "It had to be, right?", "qSentId": 633}, {"answer": "Oh, dear.", "docId": "130206pmt", "aSentId": 648, "question": "Who is the worst judge on television at the moment?", "qSentId": 647}, {"answer": "You know, I did it.", "docId": "130206pmt", "aSentId": 680, "question": "Why is that?", "qSentId": 679}, {"answer": "Without really being specific to categories, I can tell you the songs that really sort of resonated with me.", "docId": "130206pmt", "aSentId": 695, "question": "Who is your money on for big award winners?", "qSentId": 694}]